Friends, when I was travelling in the metro,
I came to know how Digital
India is changing today.  In what way is
innovation coming into the country?  Hello friends,
I am Virendra Kumar Raghav, I
welcome you all to Future Invest 2026 channel.
You are looking for finance knowledge and
how you can make finance your happy journey.
How
can you improve your portfolio by investing?  Friends, about Menu Life
Innovation Opportunity Fund and
Mahindra Mutual Fund has started a new NFO.  This
is a very good step in the innovation sector and if you are looking to invest in mutual funds and
innovation
then this fund can be for you.
Friends, how has Innovation Mutual Fund
generated good returns?  Can you also
improve your portfolio by investing in this type of mutual fund?  So friends,
do watch the video till the end because you will
get financial knowledge in it and
how you can travel from SIP of Rs 1500 to Rs 50 lakh
and in the last I will
tell you how ICIC Mutual Fund has
doubled the money in 2 years,
friends.  So friends, I am going to give you such
advice that
will help your portfolio grow and your
financial journey will be very good friends
and I will tell you what stocks to purchase in the innovation sector
or
invest through mutual funds.  Friends,
please watch the video till the end
so that you will get financial knowledge.
Along with this you will get a method of making an investment, in
which way you
can make a good investment and whether you should make a
long term investment or a
short term investment.  We will
discuss both aspects.  You will
watch the video and must like the video and
subscribe to the channel so that you
get notification of upcoming videos.  Friends,
you should keep getting information from time to time about the upcoming NFOs and
which new funds are coming in mutual funds, which
such stocks are coming?  Where to
invest?  So, you will keep
getting this type of knowledge regarding investment on this channel.  Therefore, if you
subscribe to the channel,
you will keep getting these notifications timely.
Friends, let us talk about
how a
resolution is coming in the innovation sector and how we
can make our portfolio good by investing.  Friends, Mahindra Manual
Lef Innovation Opportunity Fund, an NFO is coming
which we call New Fund Offer.   The
minimum SIP amount for investing in this fund is ₹1000.
Friends, you can invest with a minimum lump sum of ₹5,000.  There are two types of
investment options available in this.
You can invest in your regular plan.
Friends, you can invest in another direct plan.  To
invest, you can directly
visit the Mahindra Manul Lef website
or you
can invest in this fund by consulting your financial advisor.
Friends Mahindra manual Life
Innovation Opportunity Fund NFO start
date is 9th January 2026 friends and NFO
close date is 23rd January 2026.  To invest here, if
you invest between January 9 and January 23,
you will get a pricing at NAV of ₹10.
Whenever an NFO
starts, its NAV
starts from ₹10.  Friends, as I am
telling you,
in which sectors are innovations investing to
make their portfolio good.
Making your company better.  Friends,
new technologies are coming.  All the
new technologies that are coming, all the
revolutions that are taking place, you are seeing
how India is growing,
Digital India is happening and
innovative sectors are coming up there through new technologies.
Friends, as you see, there
is Google Pay, PhonePe, Paytm or you are
also making payments through new technologies through WhatsApp.
Or you are seeing
new technology electric vehicles coming.
Solar panels are coming or
AI in electric vehicles, so here
you have new applications like chat GPS.
New data is coming in.  From where you
can innovate yourself and invest
in this type of innovative sector.
As you
can see, a very good innovation is taking place in the banking sector also.
Where
transactions through UPI are increasing day by day.  Friends, if
I talk about stocks, where are you investing
in this innovation sector?
So, stock wise,
I will tell you
in which stocks this fund
will invest and how the fund manager will
manage this fund as per his understanding so that
you get
good returns in the future and this fund is
for those people who want to invest between 5 years to 10 years
or
they have a long term vision and want to invest for 15 years or 20
years, this fund can be good for them,
friends, this
is not a recommendation video or an advisory video from any company
that you should invest in this fund.  You
can invest in this fund by consulting your financial advisor or through the website or anywhere else or as per your own research.
So in the video we will tell you further
in which stocks this fund is
likely to invest.
Where will the fund manager invest?
If I talk about stock price then
ICICI Bank B Airtel Infosys Maruti
Suzuki Axis Bank Mahindra & Mahindra
LTD Computer Age Management Services LTD
NTBC God Consumer Mankind Pharma LTD TVS
Motors Blue Star LTD HDFC Life
Insurance
Br Enterprises Friends, here you have
seen that this fund manager has
tried to pick many stocks here, so in this way the
fund manager will
pick big stocks.  From where there are
possibilities of big innovations coming.  You can see that
innovation is increasing day by day.
And as companies work in the innovation sector.
Their demand is to
invest in big innovation companies.  If
you are looking to create wealth in the long term, then
this fund can be best for you.
Friends, as
I told you in the beginning of the video, I will
tell you about a fund in
which you
can make ₹50 lakh in 21 years with an SIP of ₹1500.  Friends,
if you invest ₹50 every day and
invest in it for 21 years and
step up by 10% every year, then
after the next 21 years you will have a fund of ₹50 lakh
ready, friends.  Friends, mutual
funds are not for short term.
With an SIP of ₹1500, you can create a fund of ₹50 lakh.
You have to do SIP continuously
and top up it by 10% every year
so that you can have ₹50 lakh in the future.
Friends, as I was
telling you, friends, let me take an example of
ICICI Pashul Innovation Fund which
started in May 2023 and the fund has completed almost 2 years, the
NV of that fund has become 19.66 paise
and the fund has
given a return of about 28.10% till now.  Friends,
suppose an investor had invested ₹1 lakh
in May 2023 ICICI PSE NFO, then
today the value of that fund would have been approximately ₹1 lakh.
So friends, if you want to
achieve your goals by investing in the innovation category, then in
this way, the time given for investing in Mahindra Manual
Life Innovation Opportunity Fund is from
9th January to
23rd January.
If you want
your investment to be at a NAV of ₹10, then
you can invest in this fund.
So to watch such videos,
please subscribe to the channel and like the video.  Thank you very much friends.
Hello.